it's frustrating that many Canadians
aren't covered for expenses like dental
care and prescription drugs even if you
have coverage at work it may not be
enough that's where Flex care from
manite comes in Flex care offers a
variety of dental and health plans for
you and your family and best of all you
only pay for the coverage you want plans
start at under $3 a day and flexcare is
Lifetime coverage so it continues as
long as premiums are paid regardless of
your age or if your health changes
what's more Flex care has a 30-day
moneyb guarantee and an easy access card
just present your Flex care card at most
dental offices and pharmacies and you're
good to go let's review the coverage
Flex care offers expenses like
prescription drugs dental and vision
Care Plus unexpected expenses like
physiotherapy Chiropractic Care and More
for a limited time get 50 Air Miles
reward miles when you call for your no
obligation quote and remember Flex care
has a 30-day moneyback
guarantee call 1844 664 Flex today for
your free no obligation quote and get 50
Air Miles reward
[Music]
miles Flex care from manual
life